<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sticky Sticky Notes</string>
    <string name="app_icon">Application icon</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="have_a_nice_day">And have a nice day!</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="password">Passsword</string>
    <string name="ip_address">Server address</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="encountered_problem">Ecountered problem</string>
    <string name="try_again">Retry</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="network_error_no_code">Unknown problem. More informations:</string>
    <string name="ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="wrong_url_format">Wrong url format. Url should begin with \'http\' or \'https\' prefix.</string>
    <string name="new_user_title">New user</string>
    <string name="new_user">New user has been created. You can login into your account now.</string>
    <string name="network_with_error_code_400">400 Bad Request – The server cannot or will not process
        the request due to something that is perceived to be a client error (e.g., malformed request syntax,
        invalid request message framing, or deceptive request routing).</string>
    <string name="network_with_error_code_401">401 Unauthorized – The server generating a 401 response MUST
        send a WWW-Authenticate header field containing at least one challenge applicable to the
        target resource.</string>
    <string name="network_with_error_code_403">403 Forbidden – The request was valid, but the server
        is refusing action. The user might not have the necessary permissions for a resource, or may
        need an account of some sort.</string>
    <string name="network_with_error_code_404">404 Not Found – The requested resource could not be
        found but may be available in the future. Subsequent requests by the client are permissible.</string>
    <string name="network_with_error_code_408">408 Request Timeout – he server timed out waiting for
        the request. According to HTTP specifications: "The client did not produce a request within the time
        that the server was prepared to wait. The client MAY repeat the request without modifications
        at any later time.</string>
    <string name="network_with_error_code_410">410 Gone – Indicates that the resource requested is
        no longer available and will not be available again. This should be used when a resource
        has been intentionally removed and the resource should be purged.</string>
    <string name="network_with_error_code_500">500 Internal Server Error – The server encountered an
        unexpected condition that prevented it from fulfilling the request.</string>
    <string name="network_with_error_code_502">502 Bad Gateway – The server, while acting as a gateway
        or proxy, received an invalid response from an inbound server it accessed while attempting to
        fulfill the request.</string>
    <string name="network_with_error_code_503">503 Service Unavailable –The server is currently unable to
        handle the request due to a temporary overload or scheduled maintenance, which will likely be
        alleviated after some delay.</string>
    <string name="network_with_error_code_504">504 Gateway Timeout – The server was acting as a gateway
        or proxy and did not receive a timely response from the upstream server.</string>
    <string name="network_with_error_code_unknown">Unknown networking problem. More informations:</string>
    <string name="empty_note_message">Touch this note to change it.</string>
    <string name="remove_dialog_title">Removing item</string>
    <string name="remove_dialog_message">Would you like to remove selected item?</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="change_server">Change server</string>
    <string name="set_new_address">Set new address</string>
    <string name="enter_address">Enter new server address:</string>


    <!-- Strings used as variables or as constant values -->
    <string name="animation_transition_notes_to_editor">NOTES_TO_EDITOR</string>
    <string name="animation_transition_note_background">NOTE_BACKGROUND</string>
</resources>
